import { UnderlineText,  SquareRoot, superscript, subscript, BoldText, ItalicText, Fraction, ShortFraction, LongFraction, MixedFraction, Isotopes } from "@/mathnotation"


export const ENGLISHLANGUAGEA2001 = [

{
section: "1",
instruction: "In each of the following sentence, there is one word or group of words underlined word and one gap. From the list of words or group of words lettered A to D, choose the one that is most noarly opposite in meaning to the underlined word or group of words and that will, at the same time, correctly fill the gap in the sentence.",
id: "question1",
question: ["1. The leader delegation was ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"commended"}/>, " for the manner in which he handled the matter, while their hosts of the were ______________"],
A: "applauded",
B: "praised",
C: "criticized",
D: "sanctioned",
answer: "C. criticized",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question2",
question: ["2. Musa is very  ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"frugal,"}/>, " whereas his friend Audu is ______________"],
A: "miserly",
B: "thrifty",
C: "precocious",
D: "extravagant",
answer: "D. extravagant",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question3",
question: ["3. Taiwo's ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"flamboyance"}/>, " and Kesinde's ______________ often keep people wondering if they are really twins"],
A: "modesty",
B: "arrogance",
C: "timidity",
D: "pretension",
answer: "A. modesty",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question4",
question: ["4. People enjoy stories with ______________ rather than those with ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"far-fetched"}/>, " backgrounds"],
A: "practical",
B: "realistic",
C: "artificial",
D: "undefined",
answer: "B. realistic",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question5",
question: ["5. We were asked to reach a ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"compromise"}/>, " and not start another ______________"],
A: "accusation",
B: "concession",
C: "controversy",
D: "issue.",
answer: "C. controversy",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question6",
question: ["6. He was promoted for his ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"efficiency,"}/>, "  while his colleague was demoted for ______________"],
A: "ability",
B: "lateness",
C: "incompetence",
D: "capability",
answer: "C. incompetence",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question7",
question: ["7. Oken's business is ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"flourishing"}/>, "  while his father's is...."],
A: "declining",
B: "progressing",
C: "withering",
D: "vanishing",
answer: "A. declining",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question8",
question: ["8. You should be ______________ So as not to be caught  ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"unawares"}/>, ""],
A: "serious",
B: "sober",
C: "ready",
D: "alert",
answer: "D. alert",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question9",
question: ["9. The manager who was ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"sacked"}/>, " last month has been ______________"],
A: "retired",
B: "suspended",
C: "reinstated",
D: "promoted",
answer: "C. reinstated",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question10",
question: ["10. The school authorities expected the contributions to be ______________ rather than ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"compulsory"}/>, ""],
A: "wilful",
B: "voluntary",
C: "deliberate",
D: "out wrong",
answer: "B. voluntary",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
section: "2",
instruction: "From the words lettered A to D, choose the word that bost complotos each of the following sentences.",
id: "question11",
question: "11. The ______________ programme against childhood diseases has ended.",
A: "injection",
B: "vaccination",
C: "immunization",
D: "harmonization",
answer: "C. immunization",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question12",
question: "12. The accused stated ______________ that he was innocent of the crime.",
A: "unequivocally",
B: "feebly",
C: "assamedly",
D: "excitedly.",
answer: "A. unequivocally",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question13",
question: "13. The doctor's ______________ was that the patient was suffering from cancer.",
A: "prediction",
B: "verdict",
C: "diagnosis",
D: "analysis.",
answer: "C. diagnosis",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question14",
question: "14. I was advised to open a ______________ account with the bank if I wanted to pay in cheques",
A: "savings",
B: "deposit",
C: "loans",
D: "current",
answer: "D. current",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question15",
question: "15. The pastor addressed his ______________ in a sonorous voice.",
A: "audience",
B: "masses",
C: "spectators",
D: "congregation",
answer: "D. congregation",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question16",
question: "16. Many African leaders try to cling ______________ to power.",
A: "tenaciously",
B: "judiciously",
C: "economically",
D: "socially",
answer: "A. tenaciously",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question17",
question: "17. The civilian head of state was __________ in a military coup d’état",
A: "discharged",
B: "ousted",
C: "empowered",
D: "enthroned",
answer: "B. ousted",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question18",
question: "18. After much debate on the controversial issue, the meeting was ______________ till the next morning.",
A: "postponed",
B: "proscribed",
C: "adjourned",
D: "delayed.",
answer: "C. adjourned",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question19",
question: "19. The company distributed gifts to its staff as an ______________ to hard work.",
A: "incentive",
B: "inception",
C: "interest",
D: "induction",
answer: "A. incentive",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
section: "3",
instruction: "After each of the following sentences, a list of possible interpretations are given. Choose the interpretation that you consider most appropriate for each sentence.",
id: "question20",
question: "20. Bukola has an infectious smile. means that Bukola __________ ",
A: "spreads infection when she smiles.",
B: "has sores in her teeth.",
C: "makes others smile when she smiles",
D: "becomes infected when she smiles.",
answer: "C. makes others smile when she smiles",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question21",
question: "21. It is cold comfort to tell a hungry man that starvation improves health. This means that telling a hungry man this is ______________.",
A: "frightening",
B: "consoling",
C: "unselpful",
D: "hypocritical.",
answer: "C. unselpful",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question22",
question: "22. Nonso's father gave him a free hand to run the family business. The means that his father ______________.",
A: "assisted him freely.",
B: "allowed him to make decisions.",
C: "made him sole owner of the business",
D: "allowed him freedom of movement in the premises",
answer: "B. allowed him to make decisions",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question23",
question: "23. Audu was certainly born with a silver in his mouth. This means spoon that.",
A: "he was in a rich family.",
B: "his parents gave him silver spoon when he was born",
C: "he was bon in the age of miracle",
D: "his parents could not help him..",
answer: "A. he was in a rich family",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question24",
question: "24. You must be speaking with your tongue in your cheek. This means that you _____________",
A: "must be very serious",
B: "must be thinking of something else",
C: "have food in your mouth",
D: "don't mean what you are saying",
answer: "D. don't mean what you are saying",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question25",
question: "25. The manager hit the roof when he was presented with a huge estimate for the new project. This means that the manager ____________",
A: "become very suspicious.",
B: "threw an object at the roof.",
C: "become very angry.",
D: "ordered the project to be started at once.",
answer: "C. become very angry",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question26",
question: "26. Her reproaches cut him to the quick. This means that he ______________",
A: "was made to act quickly",
B: "was wounded",
C: "was deeply hurt",
D: "began to speak angrily.",
answer: "A. was made to act quickly",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question27",
question: "27. The girl went scot-free even though she started the fight. This means that the girls was.",
A: "punished",
B: "unpunished",
C: "expelled from school.",
D: "free to move about",
answer: "B. unpunished",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question28",
question: "28. This secretary's vote of thanks did not ring true. This means that the vote of thanks was",
A: "full of praise",
B: "not audible",
C: "not sincere",
D: "well delivered",
answer: "C. not sincere",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question29",
question: "29. Mary Onyali won the race by a hair's breadth. This means that Mary won ________________",
A: "convincingly",
B: "narrowly",
C: "comfortably",
D: "luckily.",
answer: "B. narrowly",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
section: "4",
instruction: "From the words lettered A. to D below each of the following sentences, choose the word that is nearest in meaning to the underlined word as it is used in the sentence.",
id: "question30",
question: ["30. The criminal was  ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"incarcerated"}/>, ""],
A: "arrested",
B: "pardoned",
C: "imprisoned",
D: "cautioned.",
answer: "C. imprisoned",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question31",
question: ["31. The Manager soon found out that my sister was a  ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"competent"}/>, " typist."],
A: "patient",
B: "capable",
C: "hardworking",
D: "careless",
answer: "B. capable",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question32",
question: ["32. At the  ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"inception"}/>, " of his administration, the Governor was very popular"],
A: "end",
B: "beginning",
C: "dissolution",
D: "peak",
answer: "B. beginning",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question33",
question: ["33. The businessman  ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"anticipated"}/>, " the collapse of the bank"],
A: "prevented",
B: "caused C.",
D: "pre-empted",
answer: "C. foresaw",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question34",
question: ["34. The  ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"plaintiff"}/>, " was dissatisfied with the decision of the count."],
A: "solicitor",
B: "accused",
C: "complainant",
D: "respondent",
answer: "C. complainant",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question35",
question: ["35. The judge was  ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"incorruptible"}/>, ""],
A: "frank.",
B: "unreliable",
C: "incorrigible",
D: "honest.",
answer: "D. honest",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question36",
question: ["36. Mr. Preye is a  ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"stern"}/>, " father"],
A: "wicked",
B: "loving",
C: "conservative",
D: "strict",
answer: "D. strict",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question37",
question: ["37. My first son is an unusually  ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"audacious"}/>, " boy."],
A: "daring",
B: "clever",
C: "cowardly",
D: "mischievous",
answer: "A. daring",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question38",
question: ["38. Amina often makes  ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"derogatory"}/>, " remarks about her husband"],
A: "arrogant",
B: "belittling.",
C: "laudable",
D: "discreet.",
answer: "B. belittling",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
section: "5",
instruction: "Form the words or group of words lettered A to D, choose the word or group of words that best completes each of the following sentences:",
id: "question39",
question: "39. For such a serious offence, Etim was lucky to ______________ with a fine.",
A: "get over",
B: "get on",
C: "get away",
D: "get off.",
answer: "C. get away",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question40",
question: "40. The members of the Association were just rounding ______________ their discussion when the police arived",
A: "up",
B: "off",
C: "of",
D: "in",
answer: "B. off",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question41",
question: "41. I could not attend the meeting, so I asked my sister to stand ______________ for me.",
A: "up",
B: "by",
C: "in",
D: "on",
answer: "C. in",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question42",
question: "42. I tendered for that contract, but my application _______________ ",
A: "fell in",
B: "fell off",
C: "fell through",
D: "fell down.",
answer: "C. fell through",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question43",
question: "43. He is Mr. Bello's son, ______________ ?",
A: "isn't he",
B: "isn't it",
C: "is it",
D: "he is",
answer: "A. isn't he",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question44",
question: "44. You will help me with my assignment, ______________ ?",
A: "can you",
B: "could you",
C: "would you",
D: "won't you",
answer: "D. won't you",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question45",
question: "45. I bought my ________________ today.",
A: "very green first party dress",
B: "green very party first dress",
C: "first green very party dress",
D: "very first green party dress.",
answer: "D. very first green party dress",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question46",
question: "46. Although he was not born in Yoruba land, ______________",
A: "he can't speak the language",
B: "he can't write the language",
C: "he can speak the language",
D: "but he can speak the language",
answer: "C. he can speak the language",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question47",
question: "47. Adaku and Udoka curious were curious ______________ who was coming to see their father.",
A: "at",
B: "about",
C: "in",
D: "of",
answer: "B. about",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question48",
question: "48. Moji says she is better at Maths ______________",
A: "as me",
B: "than I am",
C: "as I am",
D: "with me",
answer: "B. than I am",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question49",
question: "49. I have never ______________ humiliated in my life. stomach.",
A: "being so",
B: "so being",
C: "been so",
D: "so been.",
answer: "C. been so",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question50",
question: "50. He ______________ the scene before that accident occurred.",
A: "leaves",
B: "has left",
C: "left",
D: "had left",
answer: "D. had left",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question51",
question: "51. The proposer's argument was ______________ convincing than that of his opponent",
A: "much more",
B: "most",
C: "much",
D: "more much",
answer: "A. much more",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question52",
question: "52. The cloth is _____________ wrong for my liking",
A: "very",
B: "so",
C: "quite",
D: "too",
answer: "D. too",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question53",
question: "53. By the time they arrive, we ______________ the work",
A: "shall have finished",
B: "could have finished",
C: "will finish",
D: "have finished",
answer: "A. shall have finished",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question54",
question: "54. This engine is ______________ that one.",
A: "superior than",
B: "more superior than",
C: "more superior to",
D: "superior to",
answer: "D. superior to",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question55",
question: "55. Janet could not attend the party because she ______________ with the flu over the weekend.",
A: "came up",
B: "came down",
C: "came away",
D: "came in",
answer: "B. came down",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question56",
question: "56. The new student made a good impression ______________ the rest of the class.",
A: "with",
B: "at",
C: "on",
D: "for",
answer: "C. on",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question57",
question: "57. Could I borrow ______________ cash please?",
A: "a little",
B: "a few",
C: "much",
D: "few",
answer: "A. a little",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question58",
question: "58. It is ______________ this background that we can understand the issues clearly.",
A: "for",
B: "against",
C: "with",
D: "on",
answer: "B. against",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question59",
question: "59. The teacher told the pupils to commit the poem ______________ memory.",
A: "to",
B: "in",
C: "onto",
D: "inside",
answer: "A. to",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question60",
question: "60. _____________ we waited, Ayo read the letter over again.",
A: "While",
B: "When",
C: "Where",
D: "Why",
answer: "A. While",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question61",
question: "61. I expect everybody to respect  ______________",
A: "itself",
B: "ourselves",
C: "himself",
D: "oneself",
answer: "C. himself",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question62",
question: "62. You are ______________ for having that painful experience.",
A: "none the best",
B: "none the worst",
C: "none the worse",
D: "nonetheless",
answer: "B. none the worst",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question63",
question: "63. _____________ is not good for children.",
A: "To have skipped breakfast",
B: "Skip breakfast",
C: "To have been skipping breakfast",
D: "Skipping breakfast",
answer: "D. Skipping breakfast",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question64",
question: "64. The manager is leaving the company to ______________ a new appointment elsewhere.",
A: "take over",
B: "take on",
C: "take up",
D: "take off.",
answer: "C. take up",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question65",
question: "65. Since we were not given all the things we requested, we should ______________ with what we have.",
A: "make up",
B: "make out",
C: "make do",
D: "make over",
answer: "C. make do",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question66",
question: "66. Nigerians will have ______________ to blame for withdrawing from the competition at the last minute.",
A: "themselves",
B: "one another",
C: "each other",
D: "ourselves",
answer: "A. themselves",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question67",
question: "67. Many people do not ______________ their religious professions.",
A: "live by",
B: "live to",
C: "live with",
D: "live on",
answer: "D. live on",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question68",
question: "68. _________________ a new teacher, she does not know much about the besaviour of the students.",
A: "Being",
B: "Having been",
C: "Been",
D: "Having being",
answer: "A. Being",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question69",
question: "69. The principal hoped that he ______________ to help the students.",
A: "can be able",
B: "is able",
C: "would be able",
D: "must be able",
answer: "B. is able",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question70",
question: "70. The lecturer arrived exactly ______________ time to give the talk.",
A: "on",
B: "with",
C: "by",
D: "in",
answer: "A. on",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question71",
question: "71. Olumide initially disliked Mathematics, but _______________ time he began to like it.",
A: "by",
B: "on",
C: "with",
D: "at",
answer: "C. with",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question72",
question: "72. The judge says that no one is ______________ the law",
A: "over",
B: "above",
C: "after",
D: "across",
answer: "B. above",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question73",
question: "73. The officer ______________ that he was not supposed to talk to the press on the matter.",
A: "will know",
B: "shall know",
C: "could have known",
D: "should have known",
answer: "D. should have known",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question74",
question: "74. He is a dare-devil; I really ________________ be surprised that he has escaped.",
A: "ought to",
B: "oughtn't",
C: "could",
D: "couldn't",
answer: "D. couldn't",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question75",
question: "75. This is Bisi's handwriting: there ______________ be no argument about it.",
A: "will",
B: "may",
C: "might",
D: "can.",
answer: "D. can",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
section: "6",
instruction: "In the following passages, the numbered gaps indicate missing words. Against each number in the list below each passage, four options are offered in columns lettered A to D. Choose the word that is the most suitablo to fill the numbered gap in the passages.",
passage: "Jide bought his car last year and now there is the need to renew the -76-. The first time he went to Mr. Olumide, the -77-, he was advised to -78- a -79- rather than -80- cover. Mr Olumide had carefully explained the merits and demerits of both types, which include the fact that one was far more -81- than the other. Now Jide has a cause to smile because of his entitlement to a no-claim - 82-. Being a careful owner-driver, he has not been involved in any -83- during the period. Unfortunately, the same could not be said for his friend, Jackson, whose car was a total -84- after a - 85- with a truck. He could not even make any claim for -86- because he was not -87- at all. Jackson's experience clearly points to the need for insurance -88- to educate prospective -89- on the benefits of insurance.",
id: "question76",
question: "76. *********************",
A: "road worthiness",
B: "chassis",
C: "insurance policy",
D: "vesicle dues",
answer: "C. insurance policy",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question77",
question: "77. *********************",
A: "road superintendent",
B: "insurance broker",
C: "drawing instructor",
D: "licensing officer",
answer: "B. insurance broker",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question78",
question: "78. *********************",
A: "take out",
B: "take up",
C: "take on",
D: "take in",
answer: "B. take up",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question79",
question: "79. *********************",
A: "yearly licence",
B: "yearly premium",
C: "cheaper deal",
D: "compresensive policy",
answer: "D. compresensive policy",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question80",
question: "80. *********************",
A: "second rate",
B: "first party",
C: "third party",
D: "third rate",
answer: "C. third party",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question81",
question: "81. *********************",
A: "expensive",
B: "prohibitive",
C: "exclusive",
D: "impressive",
answer: "C. exclusive",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question82",
question: "82. *********************",
A: "deduction",
B: "bonus",
C: "dividend",
D: "reward",
answer: "B. bonus",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question83",
question: "83. *********************",
A: "incident",
B: "event",
C: "accident",
D: "quarrel",
answer: "C. accident",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question84",
question: "84. *********************",
A: "wash-out",
B: "write-up",
C: "knock-out",
D: "write-off",
answer: "D. write-off",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question85",
question: "85. *********************",
A: "collision",
B: "collusion",
C: "contact",
D: "confrontation",
answer: "A. collision",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question86",
question: "86. *********************",
A: "damage",
B: "repair",
C: "damages",
D: "improvement",
answer: "C. damages",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question87",
question: "87. *********************",
A: "endorsed",
B: "recognized",
C: "insured",
D: "authorized",
answer: "C. insured",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question88",
question: "88. *********************",
A: "agents",
B: "vendors",
C: "administrators",
D: "dealers",
answer: "A. agents",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question89",
question: "89. *********************",
A: "customers",
B: "buyers",
C: "clients",
D: "applicants",
answer: "C. clients",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
passage: "The persistent fuel -90- in the country paralysed all aspect of life especially in the cities. The streets were often -91- of the usual hustle and -92- that characterised city life. A visitor might erroneously think it was a public holiday, until he came near a -93-. there he would fine long -94- of haphazardly parked vesicles waiting to buy the non-existent fuel from the idle -95-. Another look at the bus stops would reveal groups of people anxiously trying to get to their places of work. Even car owners used the few -96- buses, the drivers of which had increase the -97- by anything from 100 to 500%. Though this could be very annoying, -98- should not blame the drivers for the -99- rates because the drivers had to pay through the nose to procure fuel at the -100-",
id: "question90",
question: "90. *********************",
A: "paucity",
B: "Scarcity",
C: "withdrawal",
D: "subsidy",
answer: "B. Scarcity",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question91",
question: "91. *********************",
A: "full",
B: "derailed",
C: "deserted",
D: "devoid",
answer: "D. devoid",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question92",
question: "92. *********************",
A: "struggle",
B: "bustle",
C: "juggle",
D: "tussle",
answer: "B. bustle",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question93",
question: "93. *********************",
A: "market place",
B: "park",
C: "filling station",
D: "fuel depot",
answer: "C. filling station",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question94",
question: "94. *********************",
A: "columns",
B: "crowds",
C: "lines",
D: "queues",
answer: "D. queues",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question95",
question: "95. *********************",
A: "hands",
B: "pumps",
C: "motors",
D: "tanks.",
answer: "B. pumps",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question96",
question: "96. *********************",
A: "inaccessible",
B: "available",
C: "agreeable",
D: "pliable",
answer: "B. available",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question97",
question: "97. *********************",
A: "fees",
B: "levies",
C: "fares",
D: "money",
answer: "C. fares",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question98",
question: "98. *********************",
A: "transporters",
B: "voyagers",
C: "conductors",
D: "passengers",
answer: "D. passengers",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question99",
question: "99. *********************",
A: "exorbitant",
B: "moderate",
C: "exquisite",
D: "fair",
answer: "A. exorbitant",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question100",
question: "100. *********************",
A: "back door",
B: "black market",
C: "fuel depot",
D: "open market",
answer: "B. black market",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},



]